Guide to the Nathaniel Gage Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Original Accession
  - RESEARCH ASSISTANTS & VISITING SCHOLARS
    - Knowles, Richard. (SCRDT) (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Lewis, Ed. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Loeding, David. (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Majasan, Joseph K. (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Marks, Joan. (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Mathiott, James E. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - McGivern, Mary Ann. Res. Asst. (Protocol), SCRDT. (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Merchant, Farida G. (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Moore, Carol (Cam) Ann. (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Morton, Anne R. (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Musa, Ibrahim. (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Nichols, Sherry. (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Nicholson, Stanley Joe. (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Oswald, Mr. James - dissertation. (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Parey, Evelore. (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Pearse, Richard. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Peters, Donald. (SUSE: CAGD) (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Olson, Richard F. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Omura, Akimichi (SU Educ.453: dissertation) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Orme, Michael. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Pinney, Robert. (SUSE) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Podlogar, Maria. (SUSE:CAGD) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Porteus, Ann. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Prytulak, Susan. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Quirk, Thomas. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Repa, J. Theodore. (SUSE) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Rieger, Linda. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Roosinck, Pearl. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Rosenberg, Jeffrey I. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Salomon, Gavriel. (SUSE:CAGD) (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Sawin, E. I. (post-doctoral student) (SUSE) (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Shaw, David W. (SUSE) (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Shue, Jeannie Irene. (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Shutes, Robert. (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Silverman, Michael. (SUSE) (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Simms, Dennis J. (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Smith, Helen J. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Ian. (SUSE) (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Smith, John P. (SUSE) (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Smith, Peggy H. (SUSE) (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Smith, Roulett W. (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Speidel, Judith (SUSE) (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Steele, Mrs. LaVoneia (Canada) (SUSE) (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Spring, Carlton. (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Squier, Roger. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Swanson, Scott P. (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Talbot, Christine. (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Taylor, John. (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Taylor, Terry. (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Trinchero, Robert L. (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Unruh, Waldemar R. (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Whitmore, Joanne Gamble. (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Woodbury, Carolyn. (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Yeoh, Mr. Oon-Chye. (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - SUSE Students: Corres. with, misc., 1972 Nov-1975 Jun (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - SCRDT: Research Associates: general., 1967 Jun-1968 Sep (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Alper, Ted. (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Astin, Dr. Alexander W. (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Environment for Teaching Program: Baldridge, J. V., 1970 jun-1971 May (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Beck, William., 1967 Jun-Jul (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Urie., 1967 Jan-Mar (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Brunetti, Frank (SCRDT), 1971 Mar (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Bush, Robert N. (SCRDT), 1971 Feb-1972 Jul (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Buxton, Claude E., 1973 Jun (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Daw, Dr. Robert., 1963 Apr-1966 Oct (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Fisher, Maurice D., 1971 May-Jun (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Gaff, Jerry G., 1972 Mar-1973 May (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Gowin, D. Bob (post-doctoral fellow)., 1967 May (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Dr. Hawkinshire., 1967 Sep-1972 Dec (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Heath, Robert. (SCRDT), 1970 May-1971 Sep (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Horowitz, Murray., 1962 Nov (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Hunt, J. McV., 1953 Oct-1954 Feb (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Jones, R. S., 1962 Sep (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Kerlinger, Fred N., 1964 Nov-Dec (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Kropp, Russell P., 1967 May-Jun (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Kruszewski, Dr. Krzysztof (U. of Warsaw). (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Lindeman, Richard H. (SCRDT), 1967 Feb (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Masia, Dr. Bertram B., 1972 Jan-1973 Mar (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Mason, Ward S., Director (SCRDT), 1965 Mar-1967 Dec (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Merrill, David (SCRDT), 1967 May-1968 Jan (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Milgram, Robert - visiting scholar., 1976-77 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Molnar, Sheila R.F. (SCRDT), 1967 Dec-1973 Jan (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Newcomb, Theodore M., 1955 Jun-1957 Jan (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Reimanis, Gunars. (SCRDT), 1967 Jan-Sep (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Remmers, H.H., 1948 Mar-1972 Mar (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Rosato, George (Educ. Dev. Corp.)., 1971 Sep (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Rose, Menko., 1972 May (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - COURSES - STANFORD UNIVERSITY
    - Stanford Univ. - freshman seminar., 1969 Fall (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Psych 60 - Statistics., 1971 Fall (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Educ 215 - exams, keys, misc. papers (Fall 65)., 1965 Fall (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Educ 215 - Psy 145 - exams., 1966 Fall (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Educ 215 - exams, keys, roll, etc., 1966 Fall (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Educ 215 - lecture notes., 1965 Fall-1967 Fall (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Educ 115., 1963 Spring (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Educ 215., 1963 Spring-1967 Fall (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Educ 215 - exams, keys., 1964 Fall (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Educ 215 - grades., 1964 Spring-Fall, 1963 Spring (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Educ 215., 1967 Fall (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Educ 215 (Sieber), 1967 Summer (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Educ 215., 1966 Fall (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Educ 215., 1969 Fall (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Educ 215., 1970 Fall (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Educ 215 at Stanford in Germany., 1971 Fall (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Educ 215., 1971 Fall (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Educ 215., 1972 Fall (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Educ 215., 1973 Spring (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Educ 215 Course content., 1973 Fall (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Educ 215., 1973 Fall (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Educ 215 unit tests., 1973 Fall (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Educ 215 Student info, grades, etc., 1973 Fall (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Individulal Studies., 1972 Spring (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Educ 243X., 1973 Winter (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Swopsi 9 Teaching at Soledad., 1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Swopsi., 1972 Fall (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Education 317 diff. betw. 317 a & b., 1967 Fall (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Education 317a., 1967 Winter (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Education 317b lecture notes. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Education 317b - exams, keys, letters, etc., 1967 Spring (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Education 317a., 1968 Winter (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Education 317., 1972 Nov (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Education 318., 1972 Winter (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Education 318., 1971 Winter, Spring (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Education 318., 1970 Winter (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Education 318., 1970 Winter (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Education 318., 1970 Winter (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Education 318., 1965 Summer (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Education 318., 1968 Winter (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Education 318 - misc. ditto masters. (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Education 318 - notes on course papers. (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Education 318., 1963 Winter (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Education 318., 1964 Winter (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Education 318., 1965 Winter (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Education 314 Adv. Educ. Psych I (SU-Coladarci) (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Education 314 Adv. Educ. Psych II (SU-MacDonald) (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Education 318 Adv. Educ. Psych III (SU - MacDonald), 1962 Winter (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Psy 156, Stanford in Germany., 1971 Fall (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Educ 318 - student papers., 1968 Winter (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Educ 318 - Examinations (3 copies)., 1963 Winter (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Educ 318 - examinations & keys., 1963-65 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - SCHOOL OF EDUCATION AND GENERAL MATERIAL
    - Academic Affairs, Committee for (SUSE), 1972-74 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Minutes.
    - Admissions, CPSE [Committee for Psychological Studies in Education], 1976 Mar (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Dean of the School of Education (H. Thomas James), 1967 Oct-1969 Apr (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - The Educator (SUSE News), 1972 Dec-1976 Apr (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Factor Anal. Data on MyT & TDI - Study, 1957 Spring (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Meetings - minutes., 1962-68 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Meetings - minutes., 1970-72 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Meetings - minutes., 1973-76 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Memos., 1973-76 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Freshman Advisee Students., 1972-73 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - General, SUSE., 1972 May-76 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, SUSE., 1963-73 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - MTAI - Test. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Psychological Studies in Educ. Qualifying Exams., 1970 Fall (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Purdue Teacher's Examination, "How I Teach"., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Quotes from Leed's thesis. (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Folder includes 4 negatives Cognitive Merit Study data.
    - Response sets in objective tests: Symposium MPA., 1958 May (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - SCRDT: U.S. Office of Education. General., 1967 Nov-1968 Jul (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Signif. of Diff. between Validity Coeff. for pos. & neg. items, Hotallings t-test., 1958 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Social perception tests. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - SRA Principles of Democracy test., 1961-67 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Stanford in Germany., 1971-73 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Wilhelms, Fred T., 1960-61 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - CONFERENCES, ASSOCIATIONS, UNIVERSITIES, LABS (EXCLUDING NSSE)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science., 1971 Jun-1973 Feb (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - American Association of Colleges for Teachers of Education (AACTE)., 1976 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - American Association of School Administrators., 1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP)., 1969-73 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - AAUP-AAC Project., 1968 Summer-1969 Oct (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - AAUP Study., 1969 Dec (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - AAUP., 1975 Jul 28 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - AAUP., 1960 Feb-1973 Dec (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - AAUP, Stanford Chapter., 1963 Nov-1968 Oct (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - AAUP Comm. on Improvement of Teaching., 1959 Dec (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - American Academy of Arts & Sciences. (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - American College Testing Program., 1966 Dec 2 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - American Council on Education (ACE)., 1966-73 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - ACE., 1969-70 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      Articles & reports.
    - ACE: Joint feedback project., 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - ACE: Research Advisory Comm. (#2), 1970, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - ACE: Research Advisory Comm. (#3), 1970, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - ACE: Research Advisory Comm. (#4), 1970, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - ACE: Research Advisory Comm., meeting of (#5), 1972 Feb 11 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - ACE: Research Advisory Comm., materials for meeting., 1972 Oct 2-3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - ACE: Research Advisory Comm. (#6), 1972-73 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - ACE: Research Advisory Comm. meeting., 1973 Mar 30 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - ACE: Research Advisory Comm., materials., 1972-73 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - AERA (American Educational Research Association) Readings in Educational Research., 1970-71 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - AERA, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - AERA Symposium: "Closure on Openness in Education"., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - AERA - General. (#1), 1968-83 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - AERA - Publications Comm., 1972 Apr-1974 Nov (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - AERA - meetings., 1969 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - AERA - Symposium (NLG participation with Guba paper)., 1968 Feb (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - AERA - Symposium - "The Teacher's Explaining Behavior"., 1968 Feb (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - AERA - Symposium - Instructional Technologists., 1969 Feb (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - AERA - Symposium on Environment., 1970 Mar (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - AERA - Symposium: "Teacher Behavior in Individualized Education.", 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - AERA - Symposium., 1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - AERA - Symposium "Closure on Openness in Education"., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      See also Box 13, F.11.
    - AERA - Second Handbook of Research on Teaching ( see also Box 21, F. 38), 1969-73 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - AERA - AER Journal - reviews by NLG., 1963-68 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - AERA - AER Journal., 1963-73 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - AERA - Long Range Planning Comm., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - AERA - Long Range Planning Comm., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - AERA - Long Range Planning Comm., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - AERA - Newsletters., 1967-68 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - AERA - Nominations Comm., 1967-68 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - AERA - Annual Review., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - AERA - General., 1967-68 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - AERA - Presession., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - AERA - Meetings., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - AERA - Annual Meeting., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - AERA - Meetings., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - AERA - Meetings., 1972 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - AIR (American Institutes for Research)., 1966-74 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - AIR - Creative Talent Awards Program., 1963-66 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - AIR - Meeting., 1971 Sep 4 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - AIR - Project Plan., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - APA (American Psychological Assn.)., 1956-67 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - APA - Meetings., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - APA - Convention., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - APA - Task Force E., 1960-62 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - APA - Div. 5: Div. on Evaluation & Measurement., 1949-75 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - APA - Div. 8 - Div. of Personality & Social Psychology., 1949-72 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - APA - Div. 9., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - APA - Div. 15 - merger with Div. 16., 1961-75 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - APA - Div. 15: Educational Psychology., 1962-71 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - APA - Div. 15 - Instructional Handbook for Educational Psychologists., 1964 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - APA - General, 1948-64 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - APA - General, 1967-72 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - APA - General, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - APA - Meetings, 1972 Sep 1-8 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - APA - Program., 1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - APA - Symposium on Programmed Instruction., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - APA - Symposium., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - American Sociological Society., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Association for Higher Education., 1960-67 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Association for Supervision & Curriculum Dev., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Association for Supervision & Curriculum Dev. Dev. - CSI Seminar on Teaching., 1966-70 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      Including Report, 1966, "The Way Teaching Is."
    - Association for the Advancement of Psychology., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Association of Teacher Educators, Maryland Unit., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Banff Conference on "The Education of Elementary School Teachers"., 1967 Oct (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Behavioral Sciences Center., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Berlin Conference - N.L. Gage. Oct., 1967 Oct 16-19 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Cal. Educational Research Assn., 1964-69 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - C.A.R.E. - Cal. Agency for Research in Education., 1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - CACER (Cal. Advisory Council on Educational Research), 1960-67 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - CACER., 1973, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - CACER, Meeting., 1976 May 20 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Cal. Agency for Research in Education., 1972 Oct 26 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Cal. Commission on Teacher Preparation & Licensing., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Cal. Council on Teacher Education., 1962-74 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Cal. School Board s Assn., 1972 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Cal. State Dept. of Education., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Cal. State Psychological Assn., 1962-68 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Cal., State of - Psychology Examining Comm., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Cal. Teachers Assn. (CTA) Instruction Center., 1967-75 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Canada Council., 1970-71 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Carnegie Study for Education of Educators., 1966-67 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences., 1969-72 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - Inventories., 1965-66 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      Including photo of the fellows & staff of the center, 1965 Sep.
    - Center for Coordinated Education., 1966-71 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Center for Information Services., 1972 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - College Entrance Exam. Board., 1968-75 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - College Entrance Exam. Board., 1966-68 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - College Entrance Exam. Board, materials re. college level exam. program with NLG notes., 1966-67 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Commission for Teacher Prep. & Licensing - BTES Report #3., 1976 Sep (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Council for Basic Education., 1965-73 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Council on Social Work Education., 1967-69 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Educational Data Banks Conference., 1964 Dec (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Educational Media Branch Planning Conference., 1961 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Educational Policies Commission., 1966-68 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Educational Policy Research Center - Report., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Educational Products Information Exchange Institute., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Far West Laboratory for Educational Research & Development., 1965 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Far West Laboratory for Educational Research & Development., 1966-68 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Far West Laboratory for Educational Research & Development., 1969-75 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Far West Laboratory for Educational Research & Development - Teacher Education Program Advisory Comm., 1970-72 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Far West Lab - McClure Project., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Far West Lab - Minicourses., 1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Farmington Trust - Conf. held Ditchley Park, England, 1968 Dec., 1968-69 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - FOLEB (Internationales Forschungsseminar ueber Lern- und Bildungsprozesse) - Administrative., 1970-71 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - FOLEB Handbook., 1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - FOLEB - replies to questionnaire., 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - FOLEB - Curriculum & list of books & other materials taken to conference., 1971 Jul 25-Aug 15 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - FOLEB., 1971 Fall (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - FOLEB - correspondence after Germany., 1971-73 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - FOLEB - Volume, intro. Materials., 1972-73 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - FOLEB - Bericht (Report)., 1972 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Institute for Educational Development., 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Institute for Social Research., 1968 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - lEA (International Assn. for Educational Planning)- general., 1967 Nov-1969 Jan (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - lEA - general., 1969 Feb-Dec (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - lEA - general., 1970 Mar-1972 Sep (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - lEA - general., 1972 Sep-1973 Nov (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - lEA - Handbook., 1970 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - lEA - Explanation of organization., 1971 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - lEA - Articles & reports., 1968 Feb-1969 Nov (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - lEA - Foshay forms., 1968 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - lEA - Teacher behavior study., 1970 Nov (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - lEA - Teacher behavior study., 1971 May-1972 Jun (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - lEA - Ideas & materials for SCRDT'S project., 1968 Feb-1969 Nov (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - lEA - SCRDT'S project., 1969 Dec-1970 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - lEA - Council meeting, Budapest (file 1)., 1971 Oct 25-29 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - lEA - Council meeting, Budapest (file 2)., 1971 Oct 25-29 (Box 16, Folder 30a)
    - lEA - Proposal - criticisms., 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - lEA - Conference on Teaching Proposal., 1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - lEA - Teaching-Learning Strategies Project., 1972-73 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Individualization Group., 1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - International Congress of Applied Psychology, Liege, Belgium., 1971 Jul 25-30 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - International Congress of Psychologists, Tokyo., 1972 Aug 13-19 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - International Council on Education for Teaching (ICET)., 1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - International Institute for Educa. Planning (IIEP)., 1973-74 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - IIEP- general., 1973-76 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - IIEP (folder 1)., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - IIEP (folder 2)., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 10a)
    - IIEP - "Seminar on Evaluation of Qualitative Aspects of Education", Paris., 1974 Oct (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Michigan-Ohio Regional Educational Lab (MOREL)., 1967 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Midwestern Psychological Assn., 1947-55 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Midwestern Psychological Assn., 1956-65 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - NACEL (National Advisory Committee on Educational Laboratories) - meeting agenda, papers, etc., 1968 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - NACEL - cortespondence & memoranda, 1967-68. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - NACEL - meeting agenda, papers, etc., 1967 - 68. (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - NACEL - meeting, 7/12-13/68., 1968 Jul 12-13 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - NACEL - meeting - travel info., correspondence, vouchers., 1968 Jul 12-13 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - NACEL - Educ. Dev. Center., 1968 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - NACEL - general., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - NCATE (National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education)., 1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - National Council on Measurement in Education., 1965-71 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - The NDEA National Institute for Advanced Study in Teaching Disadvantaged Youth., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - National Institute for Education., 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - National Lab. of Computer-Based Instruction., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - National Program of Educa. Laboratories (N.L. Gage, Consultant)., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - National Society of College Teachers of Education., 1964-68 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - NTL Institute for Applied Behavioral Science., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - New Jersey Education Reform Project., 1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Northwest Regional Educa. Laboratory., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Phi Delta Kappa Research Advisory Comm., 1962-68 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Phi Delta Kappa Symposium., 1963 Nov 4-5 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Phi Delta Kappa - Stanford Chapter, general., 1964-66 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - The Scottish Council for Research in Education., 1975-76 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Sigma Xi., 1940-71 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - The Society of Professors of Education (formerly National Society of ColI. Teachers of Education)., 1968-73 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - The Society of Profs. of Education - major papers and abstracts of meetings., 1968-70 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - The Society for the Psychological Study of Social Issues (SPSSI)., 1957-67 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - The Society for the Psychological Study of Social Issues., 1969-74 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Southwest Educational Dev. Lab., 1972 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Southwest Regional Laboratory for Educational Research & Devel., 1965-68 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Southwestern Cooperative Educational Laboratory, Inc., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Teacher Corps., 1973 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights., 1974 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - United States Public Health Service., 1964-68 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Universities - Case Western Reserve U., Cleveland, Ohio, Review., 1971 May 17-20 (Box 18, Folder 27)